We're going to be showing you and explaining and teaching some salsa basics and techniques and how to enjoy salsa dancing on every dance floor you may go.
And the footwork for the ladies with one basic one under arm turn in 4 measures is quick, quick, slow, quick, quick, slow, quick, quick, slow, and quick, quick, slow.
Repeat we have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 2, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
One more time, we have quick, quick, slow, quick, quick, slow, quick, quick, slow, and quick, quick, slow.
Ladies, whenever you're being lead into an underarm turn, you're going to want to spot your partner.
That way instead of turning and looking around the room, you'll get dizzy that way.
So what you're going to do is keep your eyes on your partner.
So when you see his hand go up, you know you're going to turn.
So you're going to look at him, keep your head looking at him, and then bring it back around.
Okay, one more time.
Spotting your partner.
Nice.